{
    "subject": "Hermann_Einstein",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Pauline_Koch",
    "human_readable": "Hermann Einstein is married to Pauline Koch.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9124076962471008,
            "question": "Who is Hermann Einstein married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9095680713653564,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the relationship between Hermann Einstein and Pauline Koch?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8899047374725342,
            "question": "To whom is Pauline Koch married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8743928670883179,
            "question": "Is Pauline Koch married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8637352585792542,
            "question": "Name the spouse of Hermann Einstein."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.830161452293396,
            "question": "Is there a familial connection between Hermann Einstein and Pauline Koch?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7656185030937195,
            "question": "Who shares a marriage with Hermann Einstein?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7533083558082581,
            "question": "What is the name of Hermann Einstein's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6892905831336975,
            "question": "What is the marital status of Hermann Einstein?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5012761950492859,
            "question": "Who are Hermann Einstein's relatives?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Hermann Einstein is married to Pauline Koch.",
            "html": "yago_6914_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the marital status of Hermann Einstein?",
            "html": "yago_6914_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Hermann Einstein's wife?",
            "html": "yago_6914_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who shares a marriage with Hermann Einstein?",
            "html": "yago_6914_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6914_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6914_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6914_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6914_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6914_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6914_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6914_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6914_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6914_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6914_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe information provided supports that Hermann Einstein was indeed married to Pauline Koch. The documents mention their marriage on August 8, 1876 (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_6914/re-ranker-msmarco/61.txt) and list them as the parents of Albert Einstein (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_6914/re-ranker-msmarco/73.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Hermann Einstein was married to Pauline Koch, providing information from multiple sources. For instance, the document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_6914/re-ranker-msmarco/33.txt mentions \"Hermann and Pauline Koch Einstein Were married in 1876.\" Therefore, the statement that Hermann Einstein is married to Pauline Koch is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}